(Mary:)and I, for one, am thrilled.
(Sheldon:)What?
What... Where's the judgment?
W-Where's the fire
and brimstone?
(Sheldon:)Where's the part where you tell
us we're going to Hell
(Sheldon:)and I say have you seen
the size of the bugs outside?
We're already there!
(Mary:)Obviously, I would prefer if you
weren't living out of wedlock,
(Mary:)but given
your special circumstances,
(Mary:)I'm very happy for you.
And what "special circumstances"
are those?
(Penny:)Oh, boy, I think it's
about to get bad.
(Mary:)Shelly, how do I put this?
(Mary:)By your third birthday,
you had memorized
(Mary:)over a thousand different kinds
of trains,
(Mary:)and I never imagined
(Mary:)a woman getting aboard
any of them.
(Sheldon:)What, so... You thought
I was going to be alone
(Sheldon:)for the rest of my life?
No! Just for the middle part.